<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on The BBJProjeK Blog</title>
    <link>/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on The BBJProjeK Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2021 &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.bbjprojek.org&#34;&gt;The BBJProjeK Team&lt;/a&gt;
</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2021 10:30:48 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Get Old Spotify UI back (Permanent)</title>
      <link>/posts/spotify_old/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2021 10:30:48 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/spotify_old/</guid>
      <description>The new Spotify look is nice, but everything is shifted around. This makes navigating Spotify awful. Fortunately, there is a way to get the old Spotify back.
Classic VS XPUI Design
Step 1. Downloading and Installing Old Spotify Version First, you will need to install and old Windows Spotify version of Spotify, 1.1.51.380 works for the new and the old design.
 Download Spotify 1.1.51.380 (Uptodown) / Google Drive Mirror  Once download, install the program.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installing Windows 11 on unsupported machines</title>
      <link>/posts/win11/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jul 2021 10:30:48 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/win11/</guid>
      <description>In this guide I will be installing Windows 11 on a unsupported machine, I will be using a HP Elite 8300 which has an Intel i5 3rd gen, TPM 1.2&amp;hellip;
This Elite 8300 supports UEFI and Secure Boot, also pass the RAM and GHz requirements, you can bypass these ones too but I would recommend to have 8GB or more RAM for Windows 11 (or any machine running in 2021-2022).
1. Getting the Insider Preview file First, you will need to get the ISO file.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Windows 10 Features I miss in Windows 7</title>
      <link>/posts/windows10features/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 10:30:48 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/windows10features/</guid>
      <description>As many of you know, I&amp;rsquo;ve been in Widows 7 since Jan 2021, and I&amp;rsquo;m really enjoying it. However, I found some features that I would love to have in Windows 7 as default.
1. Clipboard History This simple but useful feature built in Windows 10 let you save more than one thing in the clipboard. By pressing Win+V you will see a list of all the things you had copied in the past. It resets on reboot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A problem with the Windows Snipping Tool</title>
      <link>/posts/snipping-too-problem/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 10:30:48 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/snipping-too-problem/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever used Snipping Tool and realized that this program saves the screenshots as &amp;ldquo;.PNG&amp;rdquo; instead &amp;ldquo;.png&amp;rdquo;?
This sound a bit dumb but it might be really annoying for some users who uses this every day.
I managed to fix this big problem by editing the SnippingTool.exe
1. The Tools The tool I used to fix this problem was HxD, this program is a fast hex editor. It offers features such as searching and replacing, exporting, checksums/digests&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Useful Programs for a Better Windows 7 Experience</title>
      <link>/posts/programs7/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 10:30:48 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/programs7/</guid>
      <description>Did you just downgraded from Windows 10 to 7 and you miss some features from 10? Here I bring some useful features from Windows 10 and some extras that will give you the Windows 7 best experience
1. KatMouse The main purpose of the KatMouse utility is to be able to scroll in inactive Windows, this is the default behavior in Windows 10.
This is useful when you are working in Word and searching for references on the web, with this tool you wouldn&amp;rsquo;t need to select the Internet window in order to scroll the webpage, so you could still typing in Word while scrolling your chrome tab</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installing and Setting Up Windows 7 (2021 Edition)</title>
      <link>/posts/win7/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 10:30:48 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/win7/</guid>
      <description>In this med-long blog I will be setting up Windows 7 in 2021. Have you got tired of Windows 10? Follow me and get rid of that non-privacy OS with full of telemetry
1. Downloading necessary files The first thing we need is to download the Windows 7 ISO file. To do it, I highly recommend Microsoft Windows and Office ISO Download Tool. With this tool we will be able to download any Windows Version, including Windows 7, 8.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Enable Windows 7 Style on Windows 8.1</title>
      <link>/posts/windows7style/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2020 10:30:48 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/windows7style/</guid>
      <description>Screenshots Guide Step 1. Downloading files Download ZIP File (373MB) // Mirror
 [!NOTE] Extract the zip in a safe folder like Documents, don&amp;rsquo;t delete the folder or you&amp;rsquo;ll break some things later
 Step 2. Running the Aero Glass Setup File Path: Aero Glass Setup\setup-w8.1-1.2.5.exe
In installation uncheck &amp;ldquo;Install Theme&amp;rdquo;
Step 3. Installing Required Files from &amp;ldquo;Windows Aero 8.1.1v2.3&amp;rdquo; folder Step 3.1. Install UxStyle Path: Windows Aero 8.1.1v2.3\Required\UxStyle\UxStyle_sep23_x86_x64_Windows8.1.exe
Step 3.2. Add AeroGlass Registry File Path: Windows Aero 8.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Windows Vista Gadgets Style on Windows 7</title>
      <link>/posts/vistasidebar/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2020 10:30:48 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/vistasidebar/</guid>
      <description>As many users realized, Windows Vista sidebar.exe (most known as Desktop Gadgets), is different from the Windows 7 one, the most noticeable thing is the gradient it has on the desktop
If you want to have the Vista style on Windows 7, you can follow these steps easily.
1. Downloading the Tools First, you will need to download the following ZIP called: Vista Sidebar, it contains the sidebar files from the official build of Vista.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install Windows 8.1 alongside Windows 10</title>
      <link>/posts/windows10-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2020 10:30:48 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/windows10-8/</guid>
      <description>Installing Windows 10 and windows 8.1 version of the Microsoft Operating system is really easy as they both support Windows Boot Manager via UEFI.
In this post I&amp;rsquo;ll show you how to install both versions of Windows in your PC (UEFI).
1. Prerequisites:  At least 1 USB device (2 recommended). A Windows system. An UEFI PC (for the installation). A disk drive (2 recommended).  2. Downloading necessary files First, we&amp;rsquo;re going to download Windows 10 and Windows 8.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create an ISO File from a Folder in Windows</title>
      <link>/posts/iso/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2019 10:30:48 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/iso/</guid>
      <description>An ISO file is a container that can hold a number of files. It’s usually used to create backups of your CD and DVD discs. However, you can create an ISO from the folders on your Windows PC as well.
1. Download the required software I personally recommend the program &amp;ldquo;Folder2ISO&amp;rdquo;. Download from https://www.trustfm.net/software/utilities/Folder2Iso.php?page=Download
Folder2Iso it’s a free and portable tool that helps quickly create ISOs. It works on many versions of Windows including Windows 7, 8, 10, and Linux.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
